EZEQUIEL CASTELLANOS

FRONT-END DEVELOPER



+5493875432979

🛕 Salta, Argentina

🦪 g<u>ithub.com/EzequielCaste</u>

TECHNOLOGIES

- HTML5, CSS and JavaScript
- React.js, Next.js
- Sass, Tailwind CSS
- Node.js, MongoDB, Express
- Git and GitHub

PROJECTS

React Movie App

https://cmyk-tiger.netlify.app/

- Shows movie recommendations fetching data from the TheMovieDB.org API
- Group project which helped us implement version control with Git and GitHub
- Developed with React, React Router and Material UI

Portfolio Website

http://ezecastellanos.com.ar

- Built using Next.js and Tailwind CSS
- Responsive design for small and large screens

ABOUT ME

I have worked as an english/spanish translator for more than 10 years. This experience has allowed me to build my researching skills as well as the ability to grasp new concepts quickly. Applying these skills to help open-source projects such as The Modern JavaScript Tutorial, fullfilling the role of Maintainer of their GitHub repository in Spanish.

EXPERIENCE

Freelance Web Developer

AO COPIERS | Dec. 2020 - Apr. 2021

- Maintain and improve company website
- Implementing responsive design for mobile

Volunteer Translator

FREECODECAMP | Feb. 2021 - Present

- Translation of technical articles
- Proofreading and correction of articles

Senior Translator & Office Assistant

TORRE-PULISICH ACCOUNTING FIRM | Aug. 2014 - Present

- Translation of Accounting Reports, Board Meeting Minutes, Bylaws and Audit Reports
- Translation of emails and conference calls
- Preparation of Payment Orders and Checks

EDUCATION & TRAINING

freeCodeCamp

Mar. 2019 - Mar. 2020

Completed 6 Certifications :

- Responsive Web Design (300 hours)
- Javascript Algorithms and Data Structures (300 hours)
- Front End Libraries (300 hours)
- Data Visualization (300 hours)
- APIs and Microservices (300 hours)

Udemy

Jun. 2020 - Oct. 2020

React: From zero to expert (Hooks and MERN) by Fernando Herrera

Front End Web Development Ultimate Course 2021